freefixer.com 2019-05-06

# 

Hello, my name is Roger Karlsson and I'm running freefixer.com. This page explains how I collect, process and store personal data on freefixer.com.

## Emails

If you send an email to me, it will be downloaded over a secure connection from the mail server and stored on my local machine. I will delete the email within 14 days. When I reply to your email it is uploaded to the mail server over a secure connection. 

## PayPal

If you use PayPal to purchase or donate, PayPal will send an email about your transaction in an email to me. This email is downloaded over a secure connection from the mail server and stored on my local machine. This email contains information about you, such as your name and email address. I need your email address to send the product or to thank you in the case of a donation. The email from PayPal is deleted within 14 days. 

## The FreeFixer Software

When you are using the FreeFixer and use the links inside the software, a lot of non-personal data about the clicked item is uploaded to the web server. For example, the complete file, the name of the file, the location of the file, etc. I'm taking some steps to prevent the upload of personal data, for example, replacing your username and computer name in file or folder names. I'm also monitoring the uploaded data on a regular basis. However, it's impossible to guarantee that no personal data is located in the unstructured data that the FreeFixer software handles. If you see that some personal data is uploaded, please contact me and I'll remove it. When you choose to upload a file from the FreeFixer software, this file is also shared with www.virustotal.com. This is necessary to provide virustotal scan results on freefixer.com web site. 

## IP addresses

When you are visiting the web site your IP address is written to an [access log](https://httpd.apache.org/docs/2.4/logs.html#accesslog) by the web server. This information in needed to prevent fraud and abuse. The access log is deleted after 5 days. The most frequently used IP addresses will be saved in a long-term report. The long term report is deleted after 30 days. If fraud or abuse is detected from an IP address, it will be stored without a deletion date. 

## Google Adsense

I'm using Google Adsense to show ads on the web site. This means that Google will see your IP address and put cookies on your machine. You can read more here. 

## Google Analytics

I'm using Google Analytics on this web site to help me understand how users interact with the web page. This means Google will see you IP address and put cookies on your machine. You can read more here. 

## Facebook

I'm using the Facebook Like plugin on the web page. This means that Facebook will see you IP address. Facebook will also put cookies on your machine. You can read more here. 

## Server location

The web server is located in the US. Dreamhost is my hosting provider.
